Office of Undergraduate Education Records UA049
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Office of Undergraduate Education Records
1985 -- 2013
1940 -- 2018
Digital Collections and Archives, Tufts University
Dean of Undergraduate Education
Dean of Undergraduate Admissions and Enrollment Management
Associate Dean for Undergraduate Curriculum Development
UA049
80.8 Linear Feet 70 boxes and 1 oversize folder
23 Digital Object(s) 23 digital objects comprising 181 files.
9.5 Megabytes
Arrangement
This collection is organized into eight series: Subject files; Committees; Publications; Plan of study; Student files; Degree sheets; Dean of Undergraduate Education records; and Unprocessed accessions.
Scope and Contents
The collection contains subject files, committee records, administrative and student records from the plan of study program, publications from the Office of the Dean of Undergraduate Studies, and records from the Dean of Undergraduate Education.
Biographical / Historical
The Office of Undergraduate Education provides educational programs, academic support, and opportunities for research and post-graduate fellowships for graduate students and undergraduates in the schools of Arts and Sciences and Engineering. This office oversees undergraduate academic policy, degree requirements and the senior degree certificate, academic support and pre-major advising, and orientation events for the various schools within Tufts. As of 2014, the office was renamed the Office of Academic Advising and Undergraduate Studies after the merge of the offices of the Associate Deans of Undergraduate Education, the Academic Resource Center, and the professional advising staff. As of March 2020, the office was renamed from the Office of the Dean of Undergraduate Education to the Office of Undergraduate Education.
Conditions Governing Access
This collection contains some restricted material. Restrictions related to specific material are listed in the detailed contents list. This collection may require review before it is available for use. Please contact DCA for further details.
Student Affairs and Services
- Subject Files, 1940 -- 1989; UA049.001; 9.6 Linear Feet
  Scope and Contents
  This series consists of subject files, arranged alphabetically dating predominantly from the 1970s through the 1980s. The files contain correspondence including related statistics, administrative records, forms, and reports.
  Arrangement
  This series is arranged alphabetically.
  Conditions Governing Access
  75 years from the date of creation.
  - Academic Awards, 1980 -- 1981; UA049.001.001.00001 (Box 1)
  - Academic Fair, 1973 -- 1975; UA049.001.001.00002 (Box 1)
  - Academic Fair, 1978; UA049.001.001.00003 (Box 1)
  - Academic Resource Center, 1975 -- 1981; UA049.001.001.00004 (Box 1)
  - Academic Standing, 1978 -- 1982; UA049.001.001.00005 (Box 1)
  - Admissions, 1978 -- 1979; UA049.001.001.00006 (Box 1)
  - Admissions Office/Communication, 1976; UA049.001.001.00007 (Box 1)
  - Admissions Presentation, 1987; UA049.001.001.00008 (Box 1)
  - Admissions of Tufts Candidates to Professional Schools, 1979 -- 1980; UA049.001.001.00009 (Box 1)
  - Advanced Placement, 1976 -- 1980; UA049.001.001.00010 (Box 1)
  - Advanced Placement, 1976; UA049.001.001.00011 (Box 1)
  - Advising Coordination Letters, 1977; UA049.001.001.00012 (Box 1)
  - Advising and Counselling from N. Blagg, 1972 -- 1975; UA049.001.001.00013 (Box 1)
  - Advising: Post-Freshman, 1977; UA049.001.001.00014 (Box 1)
  - Advisors: Plans, Meetings, Etc., 1972 -- 1977; UA049.001.001.00015 (Box 1)
  - Advisor Training Workshop, May, 1977 -- 1978; UA049.001.001.00016 (Box 1)
  - African-American Center, 1978 -- 1980; UA049.001.001.00017 (Box 1)
  - Alumni Survey, 1988; UA049.001.001.00018 (Box 1)
  - American Studies, 1979 -- 1981; UA049.001.001.00019 (Box 1)
  - Annual Report: Dean of Undergraduate Studies, 1978 -- 1979; UA049.001.001.00020 (Box 1)
  - Annual Report: Dean of Undergraduate Studies, 1979 -- 1980; UA049.001.001.00021 (Box 1)
  - Annual Reports: Dean of Undergraduate Studies, 1979 -- 1981; UA049.001.001.00022 (Box 1)
  - Annual Report: Dean of Undergraduate Studies, 1981 -- 1982; UA049.001.001.00023 (Box 1)
  - Annual Report: Dean of Undergraduate Studies, 1982; UA049.001.001.00024 (Box 1)
  - Annual Report: Dean of Undergraduate Studies, 1983; UA049.001.001.00025 (Box 1)
  - Annual Report: Dean of Undergraduate Studies, 1983 -- 1984; UA049.001.001.00026 (Box 1)
  - Annual Report: Dean of Undergraduate Studies, 1984 -- 1985; UA049.001.001.00027 (Box 1)
  - Annual Reports/Undergraduate Studies Reporting Offices, 1984 -- 1986; UA049.001.001.00028 (Box 1)
  - Annual Reports/Undergraduate Studies Reporting Offices, 1985 -- 1986; UA049.001.001.00029 (Box 1)
  - Annual Reports/Undergraduate Studies Reporting Offices, 1986 -- 1987; UA049.001.001.00030 (Box 1)
  - Annual Reports/Undergraduate Studies Reporting Offices, 1987 -- 1988; UA049.001.001.00031 (Box 1)
  - Annual Reports/Undergraduate Studies Reporting Offices, 1987 -- 1988; UA049.001.001.00032 (Box 1)
  - Annual Reports/Undergraduate Studies Reporting Offices, 1989; UA049.001.001.00033 (Box 1)
  - Artist-in-Residence, 1980 -- 1981; UA049.001.001.00034 (Box 1)
  - Arts and Sciences Deans Meetings, 1986 -- 1987; UA049.001.001.00035 (Box 1)
  - Arts and Sciences Faculty, 1987 -- 1988; UA049.001.001.00036 (Box 1)
  - Arts and Sciences Faculty, 1986 -- 1987; UA049.001.001.00037 (Box 1)
  - Arts and Sciences Plans, 1986 -- 1987; UA049.001.001.00038 (Box 1)
  - Arts and Sciences Plans, 1986 -- 1989; UA049.001.001.00039 (Box 1)
  - Athletics, 1979 -- 1980; UA049.001.001.00040 (Box 1)
  - Audit of Academic Quality, 1984; UA049.001.001.00041 (Box 1)
  - Baccalaureate Address, 1982; UA049.001.002.00001 (Box 2)
  - Ballou Renovations, 1988; UA049.001.002.00002 (Box 2)
  - Blocks of Concentrated Study, 1967; UA049.001.002.00003 (Box 2)
  - Boston School of Occupational Therapy, 1979 -- 1980; UA049.001.002.00004 (Box 2)
  - Boston School of Occupational Therapy: List, 1982; UA049.001.002.00005 (Box 2)
  - Broderick, Lillian, 1980; UA049.001.002.00006 (Box 2)
  - Brown, Norman O., 1980; UA049.001.002.00007 (Box 2)
  - 1982-83 Budget, 1982 -- 1983; UA049.001.002.00008 (Box 2)
  - Budget Printouts, 1980 -- 1982; UA049.001.002.00009 (Box 2)
  - Budget Reductions, 1987 -- 1988; UA049.001.002.00010 (Box 2)
  - Budget Requests for 1984-85, 1984 -- 1985; UA049.001.002.00011 (Box 2)
  - Campus Center, 1980 -- 1981; UA049.001.002.00012 (Box 2)
  - Candidates for Degree, 1987; UA049.001.002.00013 (Box 2)
  - Career Guidance, 1983 -- 1984; UA049.001.002.00014 (Box 2)
  - Career Guidance and Placement, 1979 -- 1980; UA049.001.002.00015 (Box 2)
  - Career Guidance and Placement, 1980 -- 1981; UA049.001.002.00016 (Box 2)
  - Career Guidance and Placement, 1984 -- 1985; UA049.001.002.00017 (Box 2)
  - Career Planning Center, 1986 -- 1987; UA049.001.002.00018 (Box 2)
  - Career Planning Center, 1987 -- 1988; UA049.001.002.00019 (Box 2)
  - Child Study, 1982; UA049.001.002.00020 (Box 2)
  - Churchill Scholarship, 1980 -- 1982; UA049.001.002.00021 (Box 2)
  - CIC Minorities Fellowship Program, 1980 -- 1985; UA049.001.002.00022 (Box 2)
  - Clarke, Dorothy, 1972 -- 1974; UA049.001.002.00023 (Box 2)
  - College Within, 1970 -- 1975; UA049.001.002.00024 (Box 2)
  - Combined Degree/Dental School Program, 1982; UA049.001.002.00025 (Box 2)
  - Commencement, 1977 -- 1981; UA049.001.002.00026 (Box 2)
  - Community Health Program, 1974 -- 1981; UA049.001.002.00027 (Box 2)
  - Computer Services, 1979 -- 1980; UA049.001.002.00028 (Box 2)
  - Connor, K. Marian, 1980; UA049.001.002.00029 (Box 2)
  - Continuing Education, 1980; UA049.001.002.00030 (Box 2)
  - Correspondence with Advisors, 1972 -- 1977; UA049.001.002.00031 (Box 2)
  - Correspondence with Advisors, Fall, 1977; UA049.001.002.00032 (Box 2)
  - Correspondence, 1978; UA049.001.002.00033 (Box 2)
  - Correspondence (Carbons), 1978; UA049.001.002.00034 (Box 2)
  - Cross Registration: B.C., B.U., Brandeis, 1972 -- 1980; UA049.001.002.00035 (Box 2)
  - Curriculum Review, 1984 -- 1985; UA049.001.002.00036 (Box 2)
  - Curriculum Review, 1987 -- 1988; UA049.001.002.00037 (Box 2)
  - Curriculum Review: Data, 1984 -- 1985; UA049.001.002.00038 (Box 2)
  - Curriculum Review: Rewrite Materials, 1985 -- 1986; UA049.001.002.00039 (Box 2)
  - Curriculum Review: Statistical Information, UA049.001.002.00040 (Box 2)
  - Curtin, Elizabeth, 1980; UA049.001.002.00041 (Box 2)
  - Dance, 1980; UA049.001.002.00042 (Box 2)
  - Danforth, 1980; UA049.001.002.00043 (Box 2)
  - Dean for Freshmen, 1979; UA049.001.002.00044 (Box 2)
  - Dean, Arelston, 1979 -- 1980; UA049.001.002.00045 (Box 2)
  - Dean's Letter to Freshmen and Transfers, 1978; UA049.001.002.00046 (Box 2)
  - Dean's Meetings, 1981 -- 1982; UA049.001.002.00047 (Box 2)
  - Dean's Meetings, 1982 -- 1983; UA049.001.003.00001 (Box 3)
  - Dean's Meetings, 1984 -- 1985; UA049.001.003.00002 (Box 3)
  - Dean of Freshman Position, 1982 -- 1984; UA049.001.003.00003 (Box 3)
  - Dean of Students, 1979 -- 1980; UA049.001.003.00004 (Box 3)
  - Debate Team, 1978 -- 1980; UA049.001.003.00005 (Box 3)
  - Degree Requirements, 1966 -- 1977; UA049.001.003.00006 (Box 3)
  - Department Course Offerings, Fall, 1980; UA049.001.003.00007 (Box 3)
  - Department, Fine Arts, 1979; UA049.001.003.00008 (Box 3)
  - Department, Geology, 1980; UA049.001.003.00009 (Box 3)
  - Department, German, 1961 -- 1980; UA049.001.003.00010 (Box 3)
  - Department, History, 1967 -- 1971; UA049.001.003.00011 (Box 3)
  - Department, Mathematics, 1956 -- 1971; UA049.001.003.00012 (Box 3)
  - Department, Music, 1955 -- 1973; UA049.001.003.00013 (Box 3)
  - Department, Philosophy, 1968 -- 1973; UA049.001.003.00014 (Box 3)
  - Department, Physical Education (Men), 1965 -- 1969; UA049.001.003.00015 (Box 3)
  - Department, Physical Education (Men), 1968 -- 1969; UA049.001.003.00016 (Box 3)
  - Department, Physics, 1967 -- 1973; UA049.001.003.00017 (Box 3)
  - Department, Political Science, 1962 -- 1973; UA049.001.003.00018 (Box 3)
  - Department, Psychology, 1967 -- 1971; UA049.001.003.00019 (Box 3)
  - Department, Religion, 1967 -- 1971; UA049.001.003.00020 (Box 3)
  - Department, Sociology, 1955 -- 1974; UA049.001.003.00021 (Box 3)
  - Development, 1980 -- 1981; UA049.001.003.00022 (Box 3)
  - Development, 1984 -- 1985; UA049.001.003.00023 (Box 3)
  - Development, 1985 -- 1986; UA049.001.003.00024 (Box 3)
  - Development, 1986 -- 1988; UA049.001.003.00025 (Box 3)
  - Disabilities and Handicaps, 1977 -- 1981; UA049.001.003.00026 (Box 3)
  - Distribution Requirement, 1984 -- 1986; UA049.001.003.00027 (Box 3)
  - Diversity Programming, 1986 -- 1987; UA049.001.003.00028 (Box 3)
  - Diversity Programming, 1987 -- 1989; UA049.001.003.00029 (Box 3)
  - Dreier Protest: Protest Messages, 1982 -- 1983; UA049.001.003.00030 (Box 3)
  - Early Graduation/Part Time Study Policy, 1987; UA049.001.003.00031 (Box 3)
  - Effort Reporting System Reports, 1981 -- 1982; UA049.001.003.00032 (Box 3)
  - Environmental Handbook, 1978 -- 1979; UA049.001.003.00033 (Box 3)
  - Ethnomusicology, 1980 -- 1981; UA049.001.003.00034 (Box 3)
  - Exchange Programs, 1970 -- 1982; UA049.001.003.00035 (Box 3)
  - Experimental College, 1967 -- 1970; UA049.001.003.00036 (Box 3)
  - Experimental College, 1969 -- 1970; UA049.001.003.00037 (Box 3)
  - Experimental College, 1977 -- 1981; UA049.001.003.00038 (Box 3)
  - Experimental College, 1981 -- 1982; UA049.001.003.00039 (Box 3)
  - Experimental College, 1981 -- 1988; UA049.001.003.00040 (Box 3)
  - Experimental College Review, 1978; UA049.001.004.00001 (Box 4)
  - Experimental College Summer Grants, 1971; UA049.001.004.00002 (Box 4)
  - Exploration Leaders/Host Advisor Briefing: Orientation, 1985; UA049.001.004.00003 (Box 4)
  - Faculty Meetings, 1983 -- 1984; UA049.001.004.00004 (Box 4)
  - Faculty Meetings, Arts and Sciences, 1985 -- 1986; UA049.001.004.00005 (Box 4)
  - Faculty Orientation, Fall 1985-86, 1985 -- 1986; UA049.001.004.00006 (Box 4)
  - Faculty Responsibility, Fall 1974, UA049.001.004.00007 (Box 4)
  - Fellowship/Scholarship Materials, 1986 -- 1987; UA049.001.004.00008 (Box 4)
  - Financial Aid, 1980 -- 1981; UA049.001.004.00009 (Box 4)
  - Five Year Plan, 1963 -- 1979; UA049.001.004.00010 (Box 4)
  - Fletcher School, 1958 -- 1981; UA049.001.004.00011 (Box 4)
  - Foreign Programs, 1987 -- 1988; UA049.001.004.00012 (Box 4)
  - Four-One-Four Council, 1968 -- 1970; UA049.001.004.00013 (Box 4)
  - Four Course Program, 1959 -- 1964; UA049.001.004.00014 (Box 4)
  - Gang of 100, 1981 -- 1982; UA049.001.004.00015 (Box 4)
  - Gang of 100, Fall 1982, Spring 1983, 1982 -- 1983; UA049.001.004.00016 (Box 4)
  - Gang of 100, 1983 -- 1984; UA049.001.004.00017 (Box 4)
  - Goals Statements, 1986 -- 1987; UA049.001.004.00018 (Box 4)
  - Grades, 1969 -- 1981; UA049.001.004.00019 (Box 4)
  - Grants and Contracts, 1978 -- 1981; UA049.001.004.00020 (Box 4)
  - Gray, Christopher, 1980; UA049.001.004.00021 (Box 4)
  - Guidelines for FR Advisors (Also Law), Fall 1975, UA049.001.004.00022 (Box 4)
  - Gulf Oil Scholarship Program, 1982 -- 1983; UA049.001.004.00023 (Box 4)
  - Health Careers Opportunities Program, 1977 -- 1978; UA049.001.004.00024 (Box 4)
  - Hewlett Foundation: Final Proposal, 1984; UA049.001.004.00025 (Box 4)
  - Hewlett Foundation Grant Proposal, 1983 -- 1984; UA049.001.004.00026 (Box 4)
  - Hints for Advisors, MIT Booklet, 1971 -- 1980; UA049.001.004.00027 (Box 4)
  - Honors, 1975 -- 1982; UA049.001.004.00028 (Box 4)
  - Honors: Special Honors Program, 1972 -- 1978; UA049.001.004.00029 (Box 4)
  - Hosts, 1977; UA049.001.004.00030 (Box 4)
  - Host Program, 1975 -- 1978; UA049.001.004.00031 (Box 4)
  - Host Program: List of H.A., c.1975-78, 1975 -- 1978; UA049.001.004.00032 (Box 4)
  - Humanities, 1963 -- 1964; UA049.001.004.00033 (Box 4)
  - Humanities Program, 1979; UA049.001.004.00034 (Box 4)
  - Inst. Psychological Res., 1964 -- 1969; UA049.001.004.00035 (Box 4)
  - Institutional Reports, 1982 -- 1985; UA049.001.004.00036 (Box 4)
  - Integrated Studies Program, 1975; UA049.001.004.00037 (Box 4)
  - Integrated Studies Program, 1978 -- 1979; UA049.001.004.00038 (Box 4)
  - ICA and Fulbright Cuts Letters and Responses, 1981 -- 1982; UA049.001.004.00039 (Box 4)
  - International Office, 1978 -- 1980; UA049.001.004.00040 (Box 4)
  - International Relations Program, 1977 -- 1982; UA049.001.004.00041 (Box 4)
  - Internships, 1977 -- 1980; UA049.001.004.00042 (Box 4)
  - January Orientation, 1980; UA049.001.004.00043 (Box 4)
  - Jazz Week, 1979 -- 1980; UA049.001.004.00044 (Box 4)
  - Job Description/HMS, 1980 -- 1981; UA049.001.004.00045 (Box 4)
  - June Orientation, 1978; UA049.001.004.00046 (Box 4)
  - Law and Society Program, 1976 -- 1980; UA049.001.004.00047 (Box 4)
  - Leaves, Withdrawls, and Returns, 1971 -- 1978; UA049.001.005.00001 (Box 5)
  - Legal Studies Program, 1977 -- 1980; UA049.001.005.00002 (Box 5)
  - Letter to Students Without Advisor, October 1977, UA049.001.005.00003 (Box 5)
  - Liberal Arts and Jackson Faculty Meetings, 1986 -- 1987; UA049.001.005.00004 (Box 5)
  - Liberal Arts and Jackson Faculty, 1987 -- 1988; UA049.001.005.00005 (Box 5)
  - Lift Every Voice, 1980 -- 1981; UA049.001.005.00006 (Box 5)
  - Lilly Reports, 1983; UA049.001.005.00007 (Box 5)
  - Lists of Advisors with Hosts, Etc., UA049.001.005.00008 (Box 5)
  - Mailing to Entering Students, 1972 -- 1977; UA049.001.005.00009 (Box 5)
  - Mailing to Entering Students, 2nd Mailing (Draft), 1978; UA049.001.005.00010 (Box 5)
  - Mailing to Entering Students, 1979; UA049.001.005.00011 (Box 5)
  - Mailing to Freshmen, Class of 1981, First Mailing, Fall 1977, UA049.001.005.00012 (Box 5)
  - Mailing to Freshmen, Class of 1981, Second Mailing, Fall 1977, UA049.001.005.00013 (Box 5)
  - Mailing to Freshmen, Class of 1981, 1977; UA049.001.005.00014 (Box 5)
  - Mailing to Freshmen, 1978; UA049.001.005.00015 (Box 5)
  - Mailing to Freshmen, Sample, Summer 1978, UA049.001.005.00016 (Box 5)
  - Mailing to Freshmen, Advisors, Fall 1978, UA049.001.005.00017 (Box 5)
  - Mailing to Freshmen, Transfers, Sample, January 1978-80, 1978 -- 1980; UA049.001.005.00018 (Box 5)
  - Mailing to Freshmen, Transfers, Sample, Summer 1979, UA049.001.005.00019 (Box 5)
  - Mailing, Major Week, 1973; UA049.001.005.00020 (Box 5)
  - Majors, 1957 -- 1980; UA049.001.005.00021 (Box 5)
  - Major Week, 1974; UA049.001.005.00022 (Box 5)
  - Major Week, 1975; UA049.001.005.00023 (Box 5)
  - Major Week: Department Plans, 1973; UA049.001.005.00024 (Box 5)
  - Major Week: Suggestions, 1975 -- 1980; UA049.001.005.00025 (Box 5)
  - Marshall Scholarship, 1982 -- 1985; UA049.001.005.00026 (Box 5)
  - Master File, 1982; UA049.001.005.00027 (Box 5)
  - Matriculation, 1978; UA049.001.005.00028 (Box 5)
  - Matriculation, 1981; UA049.001.005.00029 (Box 5)
  - Maxwell, D.E., Carbons, 1981 -- 1982; UA049.001.005.00030 (Box 5)
  - Mayer, Jean, 1980; UA049.001.005.00031 (Box 5)
  - Medical Education, 1967 -- 1980; UA049.001.005.00032 (Box 5)
  - Mellon/Humanities, 1986 -- 1987; UA049.001.005.00033 (Box 5)
  - Mellon Material, 1982 -- 1983; UA049.001.005.00034 (Box 5)
  - Mental Health Program, 1974; UA049.001.005.00035 (Box 5)
  - Mid-Year Reports, 1981 -- 1982; UA049.001.005.00036 (Box 5)
  - Minor, 1979 -- 1980; UA049.001.005.00037 (Box 5)
  - Minority, 1968 -- 1980; UA049.001.005.00038 (Box 5)
  - Minority Retention, 1982 -- 1983; UA049.001.005.00039 (Box 5)
  - Minutes: Experimental College, 1964 -- 1969; UA049.001.005.00040 (Box 5)
  - Museum of Fine Arts, 1970 -- 1980; UA049.001.006.00001 (Box 6)
  - Museum School, 1983 -- 1984; UA049.001.006.00002 (Box 6)
  - New Ed Policies (grading) and Calendar, 1975; UA049.001.006.00003 (Box 6)
  - New England Conservatory, 1977 -- 1981; UA049.001.006.00004 (Box 6)
  - New England Conservatory, 1983 -- 1984; UA049.001.006.00005 (Box 6)
  - New England Conservatory, 1986 -- 1988; UA049.001.006.00006 (Box 6)
  - New England Conservatory: Travel, 1981 -- 1982; UA049.001.006.00007 (Box 6)
  - New England Deans Association, April 21, 1980; UA049.001.006.00008 (Box 6)
  - Notes on a January Orientation, 1979; UA049.001.006.00009 (Box 6)
  - Notes on Orientation, 1976 -- 1977; UA049.001.006.00010 (Box 6)
  - Office - General, 1979 -- 1982; UA049.001.006.00011 (Box 6)
  - Office of Undergraduate Studies, Plans, 1986 -- 1987; UA049.001.006.00012 (Box 6)
  - Office of Undergraduate Studies, 1987 -- 1988; UA049.001.006.00013 (Box 6)
  - Olin Foundation Proposal Language and Culture Studies Building, 1982 -- 1988; UA049.001.006.00014 (Box 6)
  - Olin Planning, 1988; UA049.001.006.00015 (Box 6)
  - Orientation, 1979 -- 1980; UA049.001.006.00016 (Box 6)
  - Orientation, Fall, 1982; UA049.001.006.00017 (Box 6)
  - Orientation, Fall, 1983; UA049.001.006.00018 (Box 6)
  - Orientation, Fall, 1984; UA049.001.006.00019 (Box 6)
  - Orientation, Fall, 1985; UA049.001.006.00020 (Box 6)
  - Orientation, Fall, 1988; UA049.001.006.00021 (Box 6)
  - Orientation Material, 1979 -- 1980; UA049.001.006.00022 (Box 6)
  - Orientation Meetings, 1977 -- 1978; UA049.001.006.00023 (Box 6)
  - Orientation Meetings, 1978; UA049.001.006.00024 (Box 6)
  - Orientation Speech, January, 1985; UA049.001.006.00025 (Box 6)
  - Outside Evaluation Report, 1982; UA049.001.006.00026 (Box 6)
  - Parent's Orientation, Fall, 1976; UA049.001.006.00027 (Box 6)
  - Parent's Weekend, 1977 -- 1980; UA049.001.006.00028 (Box 6)
  - Parent's Weekend, 1982; UA049.001.006.00029 (Box 6)
  - Parent's Weekend, October 5, 1985; UA049.001.006.00030 (Box 6)
  - Parent's Weekend, 1987; UA049.001.006.00031 (Box 6)
  - Part-Time Student Policy, 1986; UA049.001.006.00032 (Box 6)
  - Pass-Fail Option, 1966 -- 1977; UA049.001.006.00033 (Box 6)
  - Peer Advisor Briefings, UA049.001.006.00034 (Box 6)
  - Peking Foreign Language Institute, 1980 -- 1981; UA049.001.006.00035 (Box 6)
  - People for Orient: Jan 84, 1979 -- 1980; UA049.001.006.00036 (Box 6)
  - Performance Evaluations, 1986; UA049.001.006.00037 (Box 6)
  - Performing Arts at Tufts, 1980 -- 1981; UA049.001.006.00038 (Box 6)
  - Planning Your Program: Orientation, 1988; UA049.001.006.00039 (Box 6)
  - Preparing for the Real World, 1984; UA049.001.006.00040 (Box 6)
  - President's Young Scholars Program, 1986 -- 1987; UA049.001.006.00041 (Box 6)
  - President's Young Scholars Program, 1987; UA049.001.006.00042 (Box 6)
  - Princeton Visiting Student Program, 1978 -- 1980; UA049.001.006.00043 (Box 6)
  - Pueblo Nuevo, 1980 -- 1981; UA049.001.006.00044 (Box 6)
  - Reduced Course Loads, 1973 -- 1979; UA049.001.006.00045 (Box 6)
  - Registration and Scheduling, 1978 -- 1981; UA049.001.006.00046 (Box 6)
  - Report on Freshman Advising: All Information, September, 1971; UA049.001.006.00047 (Box 6)
  - Resource List, 1974 -- 1977; UA049.001.006.00048 (Box 6)
  - Resource List, Spring, 1978; UA049.001.006.00049 (Box 6)
  - Resource List, 1978; UA049.001.006.00050 (Box 6)
  - Resource List, 1979 -- 1980; UA049.001.006.00051 (Box 6)
  - Rhodes, 1978 -- 1981; UA049.001.006.00052 (Box 6)
  - Rhodes Material, 1982 -- 1983; UA049.001.006.00053 (Box 6)
  - Romance Languages, 1966 -- 1970; UA049.001.006.00054 (Box 6)
  - Rotary Foundation Scholarships, UA049.001.007.00001 (Box 7)
  - R.O.T.C., 1940 -- 1970; UA049.001.007.00002 (Box 7)
  - Scholarship Materials, 1986 -- 1988; UA049.001.007.00003 (Box 7)
  - Second International Chekhov Conference, 1982; UA049.001.007.00004 (Box 7)
  - Senior Handbook, 1971 -- 1981; UA049.001.007.00005 (Box 7)
  - Services to Engineering, 1983; UA049.001.007.00006 (Box 7)
  - S.O.A.R., 1987 -- 1988; UA049.001.007.00007 (Box 7)
  - Society of Scholars, 1958 -- 1980; UA049.001.007.00008 (Box 7)
  - Solomon, H.M.: Carbons, 1979 -- 1980; UA049.001.007.00009 (Box 7)
  - Solomon, H.M.: Carbons, 1980 -- 1981; UA049.001.007.00010 (Box 7)
  - Solomon, H.M.: Personal, 1980; UA049.001.007.00011 (Box 7)
  - Sophomore Standing, 1975 -- 1976; UA049.001.007.00012 (Box 7)
  - Sophomore Standing, UA049.001.007.00013 (Box 7)
  - Soviet and East European Area Program, 1982 -- 1984; UA049.001.007.00014 (Box 7)
  - Soviet University Exchange, 1982 -- 1983; UA049.001.007.00015 (Box 7)
  - Speeches, 1978; UA049.001.007.00016 (Box 7)
  - S.P.I.R.I.T., 1978 -- 1980; UA049.001.007.00017 (Box 7)
  - S.P.I.R.I.T., 1981 -- 1982; UA049.001.007.00018 (Box 7)
  - S.P.I.R.I.T., 1982 -- 1983; UA049.001.007.00019 (Box 7)
  - Staff Meetings, 1981 -- 1982; UA049.001.007.00020 (Box 7)
  - Staff Meetings, 1984 -- 1985; UA049.001.007.00021 (Box 7)
  - Stevenson: "This Living Hand," 1981-82, 1981 -- 1982; UA049.001.007.00022 (Box 7)
  - Students Concerned with Racism, 1968; UA049.001.007.00023 (Box 7)
  - Students Not Paid, Letter, 1979; UA049.001.007.00024 (Box 7)
  - Study Habits, 1975; UA049.001.007.00025 (Box 7)
  - Study Skills, 1965; UA049.001.007.00026 (Box 7)
  - Study Skills Seminars, 1975 -- 1978; UA049.001.007.00027 (Box 7)
  - Surveys, 1961 -- 1982; UA049.001.007.00028 (Box 7)
  - Taylor, Billy: Residency, 1979 -- 1980; UA049.001.007.00029 (Box 7)
  - Teichman, Sherman, 1986 -- 1987; UA049.001.007.00030 (Box 7)
  - Times/Places Part of Blue Booklet Master, 1977; UA049.001.007.00031 (Box 7)
  - T.O.P.S., 1978 -- 1979; UA049.001.007.00032 (Box 7)
  - Transfer of Credit People, 1974 -- 1977; UA049.001.007.00033 (Box 7)
  - Transfer Policy, 1983; UA049.001.007.00034 (Box 7)
  - Tufts Community Union Senate, 1979 -- 1981; UA049.001.007.00035 (Box 7)
  - Tufts Community Union Senate, 1981 -- 1982; UA049.001.007.00036 (Box 7)
  - Tufts Community Union Senate, 1983 -- 1984; UA049.001.007.00037 (Box 7)
  - Tufts Council on International Affairs, 1978 -- 1979; UA049.001.007.00038 (Box 7)
  - Tufts Fellowship Handbook, 1977 -- 1979; UA049.001.007.00039 (Box 7)
  - Tufts-in-Boston, 1982; UA049.001.007.00040 (Box 7)
  - Tufts/Wellesley Consortium, Underprepared Students, 1983 -- 1984; UA049.001.007.00041 (Box 7)